A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Westmoreland Davis, 1911-1922 (bulk 1918-1922)
Library of Virginia
- Series 1: General Correspondence, 1918-1922., Extent: 61 boxes (27.45 cu. ft.). (Box 1-61)
  - Newspaper interviews, 1920-1921. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper subscriptions, 1916-1919. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper subscriptions, 1920-1921. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Nitrate of Soda, 1919. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Notaries Public, 1918-1919. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Notaries Public, 1920-1922. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Notaries Public Index Cards, Accomack County - Essex County, 1918-1922. (Box 26)
  - Notaries Public Index Cards, Fairfax County - Montgomery County, 1918-1922. (Box 27)
  - Notaries Public Index Cards, Nansemond County - Norfolk, 1918-1922. (Box 28)
  - Notaries Public Index Cards, Norfolk County - Richmond, 1918-1922. (Box 29)
  - Notaries Public Index Cards, Richmond - Russell County, 1918-1922. (Box 30)
  - Notaries Public Index Cards, Shenandoah County - York County, and Commissioners of Deeds, 1918-1922. (Box 31)
  - Notaries Public, Revocation of Commissions, 1918-1921. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Nurses, 1918-1921. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Office buildings, Leases, 1918-1919. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Office building, State, Site for, 1911-1921. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Office hours (SB 196 & HB 230), 1918. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Office supplies, 1918. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Oriental University (Washington, DC), 1920-1921. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Ouster Law, 1921. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Pan American Union, 1919. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Parent-Teacher Association, 1921. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Parks, National Conference on Parks, 1920-1921. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Patents, 1918-1921. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Peanuts, 1919-1921. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Penitentiary, American Prison Association, 1918-1920. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Penitentiary, American Prison Association, 1921. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Penitentiary (Richmond, Va.), General, 1918-1919. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Penitentiary (Richmond, Va.), General, 1920. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Penitentiary (Richmond, Va.), General, 1921. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Penitentiary (Richmond, Va.), Insane Convicts, 1918-1921. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Penitentiary (Richmond, Va.), Printing Plant, 1921. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Penitentiary, State Farm (Goochland, Co., Va.), 1918-1920. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Penitentiary, State Farm (Goochland, Co., Va.), Surgeon, 1919-1920. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Penitentiary (Richmond, Va.), Prison reform, 1918-1919. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Penitentiary (Richmond, Va.), Prison reform, 1920-1921. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Pensions, General, 1918-1919. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Pensions, Confederate Veterans, 1918 February-May. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Pensions, Confederate Veterans, 1918 June-November. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Pensions, Confederate Veterans, 1919. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Pensions, Confederate Veterans, 1920 January-April. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Pensions, Confederate Veterans, 1920 June-November. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Pensions, Confederate Veterans, 1921-1922. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Pharmacy, Board of, 1918-1920. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Pharmacists, Registered, 1921. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Physical therapy, 1921. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Piedmont Sanatorium (Burkeville, Nottoway Co., Va.), 1920-1921. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Pilots, Examiners Board, 1918. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Police Chiefs, 1918-1921. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Pollution of streams, 1919. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Potatoe seed, 1918. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Press Association, 1918. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Press Congress of the World, 1921. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Probation law, 1919. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Prohibition, Federal Director, 1921. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Public printing, 1906-1920. (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Purchasing agent, State, 1918-1921. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Quantico, 1918-1919. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Quarantine Officer, Elizabeth River District, 1917-1918. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Quarantine Officer, Elizabeth River District, 1919-1920. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Railroads, Beltline Bridge (Richmond, Va.), 1919-1920. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Railroads, General, 1918-1920. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Railroads, Norfolk & Southern Railroad, 1919-1921. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Railroads, Railroad rates, 1915-1917. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Railroads, Railroad rates, 1918-1919. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Railroads, Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad, 1918-1919 May. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Railroads, Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad, 1919 June-December. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Railroads, Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad, 1920 January-April. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Railroads, Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad, 1920 May-December. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Railroads, Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad, 1921-1922 January. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Railroads, State Corporation Commission (SCC), 1919-1920. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Railroads, State Corporation Commission (SCC), 1921-1922. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Railroads, State Corporation Commission (SCC), Plumb Plan, 1919. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Railroads, Washington & Old Dominion, 1920-1921. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Red Cross, 1918 February-June. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Red Cross, 1918 July-December. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Red Cross, 1919-1920. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Rent of State Offices Fund, 1919. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Requests for information, 1918. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Rewards, Offer of for apprehension of criminals, 1918 April-June. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Rewards, Offer of for apprehension of criminals, 1918 July-December. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Rewards, Offer of for apprehension of criminals, 1919. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Rewards, Offer of for apprehension of criminals, 1920. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Rewards, Offer of for apprehension of criminals, 1921 January-June. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Rewards, Offer of for apprehension of criminals, 1921 July-1922. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Rifle Range (Virginia Beach, Va.), 1918-1920. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Rivers, National Rivers & Harbors Congress, 1919-1921. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Roads, 1918. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Roads, 1919 January-February. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Roads, 1919 March-April. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Roads, 1919 May-August. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Roads, 1919 September-December. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Roads, 1920-1921. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Roads, Federal Aid, 1916-1920. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Roads, Good Roads Association & Convention, 1918. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Roads, Good Roads Association & Convention, 1919. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Roads, Good Roads Association & Convention, 1920. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Roads, Good Roads Association & Convention, 1921. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Roads, State Highway Commission, 1919-1920. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Roads, State Highway Commission, 1921-1922. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Roads, Work of Convicts, 1918-1919. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1921. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Salvation Army, 1919-1921. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Schools, Co-Operative Education Association of Virginia, 1917-1921. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Schools, Miscellaneous, 1917-1919. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Schools, Miscellaneous, 1920-1921. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Schools, National Conference on Education, 1920-1921. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Schools, Rural, 1918. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Schools, Rural, 1919. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Schools, School Commission, 1918 February-April 15. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Schools, School Commission, 1918 April 16-1919. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Schools, Southern Education Society, 1921. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Schools, State Board of Education, 1911-1918 June. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Schools, State Board of Education, 1918 June-December. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Schools, State Board of Education, 1919 January-May. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Schools, State Board of Education, 1919 June-December. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Schools, State Board of Education, 1920. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Schools, State Board of Education, 1921 January-March. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Schools, State Board of Education, 1921 April-December. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Schools, State Board of Education, 1922. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, General, 1911-1918 March. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, General, 1918 April-December. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, General, 1919 January-April. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, General, 1919 May-1921 January. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Accomack County, 1921. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Albemarle County, 1921. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Alexandria, 1921. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Amherst County, 1921. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Appomattox County, 1921. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Arlington County, 1920-1921. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Augusta County, 1921. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Bath County, 1920-1921. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Bland County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Brunswick County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Buchanon County, 1920-1921. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Buckingham County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Campbell County, 1920-1921. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Caroline County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Carroll County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Chesterfield County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Craig County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Cumberland and Goochland Counties, 1919-1921. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Danville, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Dickenson County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Dinwiddie County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Fairfax County, 1920-1921. (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Floyd County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Fluvanna County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Gloucester County, 1921. (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Grayson County, 1920. (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Greene and Madison Counties, 1920-1921. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Greensville County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Hanover County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, King George County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, King William County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Lee County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Loudoun County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Louisa County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Mathews and Middlesex Counties, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Montgomery County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Nansemond County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Nelson County, 1920-1921. (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Newport News, NN vs. D.A. Dutrow, 1920. (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Newport News, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Northampton County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Orange County, 1921. (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Page County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Patrick County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Pittsylvania County, 1920. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Pittsylvania County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Princess Anne County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Richmond and Westmoreland Counties 1921. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Portsmouth, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Powhatan County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Prince George County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Rockbridge County, 1919-1920. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Smyth County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Southampton County, 1920-1921. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Spotsylvania County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Stafford County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Surry County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Sussex County, 1920. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Tazewell County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Washington County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, Wise County, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Schools, Superintendents of Schools, York and Warwick Counties, 1921. (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Script, 1918. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Sea training Bureau of Camp Stuart, 1920. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Second Auditor's Office, 1918-1921. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1918-1921. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of State (DC), 1919-1920. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Senate (US), Appointment, 1919. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Seheep, 1918-1920. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Smith-Howard Bill, 1918. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Socialists Labor Party, 1920-1921. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Soldiers Home (Richmond, Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Soldiers, Sailors, and Marines, Legislation for benefit ot, 1919. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - South Dakota, Rural credits law of, 1917. (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Southern Land Congress, 1919. (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Southern Commerical Congress, 1918 November-December. (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Southern Commerical Congress, 1919. (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Southern Commerical Congress, 1920. (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Southern Commercial Congress, 1921. (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Southern Sociological Congress, 1918-1919. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Spanish Battleship Alfonso XIII, 1920. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Spanish War Veterans, 1918. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Spotswood, Governor, Memorial, 1921. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - State Capitol postcards, nd. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1918. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1919-1922. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - State Depositories (banks), 1918-1920. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - State Depositories (banks), 1921. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - State entomologist and plant pathologist, 1918. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - State Fair, 1918. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - State Fee Commission, 1918-1921. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - State Library & Board, 1918-1921. (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - State Officials, Index Cards (alphabetical by cities and counties). (Box 75)
  - State Tax Board, 1918. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - State Tax Board, 1919. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - State Tax Board, 1920. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - State Tax Board, 1921. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - State Tax Board, nd. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - State Treasurer, 1918-1920. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - State Treasurer, Vouchers, 1916. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - State Treasurer, Vouchers, 1916-1918. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - State Veterinarian, 1918-1922. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Steam boilers, 1918. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Strikes, 1919-1921. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Stuart, Jeb, Monument removal, 1919. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Sugar, 1920. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Sulgrave Institution, Virginia Committee, 1919-1920. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Superintendent of Public Printing, 1919-1921. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Sunday School Rally, 1918-1921. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Tangier Island (Va.), 1918. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Tariff, Southern Tariff Congress, 1920-1921. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Taxation, 1918-1919. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Taxation, 1920-1921. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Tercentennial Celebration, 1916-1920. (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Time, Official, 1918-1920. (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Trade Mark Laws, 1919. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Treasurers of Counties, Laws relating to, 1918. (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Tuberculosis, 1918-1921. (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Uniform State Laws, Commission from Virginia, 1918-1921. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1918. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - United States, 1918-1921. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - University of Virginia, 1918-1919. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - University of Virginia, 1920-1921. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - University of Virginia, Board appointments, 1920 January. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - University of Virginia, Board appointments, 1920 February. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - University of Virginia, Richmond Memorial Road Commission, 1920. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Vault, Governor's office combination, 1918. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Veterans, Sons of, 1919. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Home and Industrial School for Girls (Richmond, Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Home for Incurables (Richmond, Va.), 1921. (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Colored Girls (Hanover Co., Va.), 1918-1920. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Manual Labor School for Colored Boys (Hanover Co., Va.), 1920. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1918. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1919. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1920. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1921. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Military Institute, Cadetship appointments, 1918-1921. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Normal Schools (Farmville, Va.), 1918-1919. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Normal Schools (Fredericksburg, Va.), 1919. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Normal Schools (Harrisonburg, Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Normal Schools (Petersburg, Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Normal Schools (East Radford, Va.), 1919-1921. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Normal Schools, Board, 1918-1919. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Normal Schools, Board, 1920-1921. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute (VPI), 1918-1919. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute (VPI), 1920-1921. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Press Association, 1918. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Virginia School for Colored Deaf and Blind Children (Newport News, Va.), 1918-1920. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Virginia State Epileptic Colony (Madison Heights, Va.), 1918. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Virginia State Fair Association, Inc., 1918-1921. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Virginia State Seal, 1919. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, 1918-1920. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Virginia War History Commission, 1919 January. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Virginia War History Commission, 1919 February-April. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Virginia War History Commission, 1919 May-December. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Virginia War History Commission, 1920-1921. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Virginia-Maryland Boundary, 1919. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Vital Statistics, Bureau of, 1918-1921. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation Education, U.S. Bureau of, 1918-1921. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Vocational Training, 1918-1919. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - War Correspondence, Adjutant General W.W. Sale, 1917-1918. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - War Correspondence, Bastille Day, 1918. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - War Correspondence, Boys, U.S. Boys Working Reserve, 1918-1919. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - War Correspondence, Burial, Unknown American Soldier of American Expeditionary Forces, 1921. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - War Correspondence, Camps (Va.), 1918. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - War Correspondence, Camps Community Service, 1918-1919. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - War Correspondence, Casualties and casualty lists, 1918. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - War Correspondence, Casualties and casualty lists, 1919. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - War Correspondence, Central Legal Advisory Council, 1918. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - War Correspondence, Chaplain, 1918. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - War Correspondence, Classification, 1918-1919. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - War Correspondence, Coast Artillery, 1918-1920. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - War Correspondence, Colleges, Military, 1918. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - War Correspondence, Committee on Public Information, 1918. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - War Correspondence, Conference on Community Organization, 1920. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - War Correspondence, Conference on the Rehabilitation of the Wounded, 1918. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - War Correspondence, Council of National Defense, 1918-1920. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - War Correspondence, Council of National Defense, Women's Committee, 1917-1918. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - War Correspondence, Council of State Defense, Women's Committee, 1918. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - War Correspondence, Conscientious Objectors, 1918. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - War Correspondence, Decorations, Military, Virginians in WWI, 1919. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - War Correspondence, Deserters, 1918-1921. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - War Correspondence, Disbursing Officer, 1918-1919. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - War Correspondence, Discharged soldiers, Registration of, 1919. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - War Correspondence, District Board, 1918-1919. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - War Correspondence, Draft exemptions, 1918 January-April. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - War Correspondence, Draft exemptions, 1918 May-November. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - War Correspondence, Draft Officers, 1918-1919. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - War Correspondence, Field glasses, Donated, undated. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - War Correspondence, Flag Day, 1918. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - War Correspondence, Furloughs, 1918-1919. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - War Correspondence, Gardeninig, 1918-1919. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - War Correspondence, Glasser, Robert, 1918. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - War Correspondence, Governors' staff uniforms, 1918. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - War Correspondence, Health index, 1918. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - War Correspondence, Home Guard, 1918-1919. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - War Correspondence, Howitzers, 1918. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - War Correspondence, Immigration Education, 1918. (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - War Correspondence, Independence Day, 1918. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - War Correspondence, Inspection, Military, 1918-1919. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - War Correspondence, Insurance, 1919. (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - War Correspondence, Italy, Military, 1918. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - War Correspondence, Judge Advocate General, 1918-1922. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - War Correspondence, Labor and Labor Day, 1918. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - War Correspondence, Land, Forms for soldiers, 1918-1919. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - War Correspondence, League of Nations, Atlantic Congress, 1919. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - War Correspondence, Legal Advisory Board, 1917-1918. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - War Correspondence, Liberty Loans, 1918-1919. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - War Correspondence, Local Boards, 1918 February-July. (Box 56, Folder 7)